Pradeep Jhuriya

Web Security Engineer/Analyst

jhuriyap@gmail.com • +917891530631

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sam5epi0l/ • https://github.com/sam5epi0l/ • https://medium.com/@sam5epi0l

Summary

A self-taught and experienced Web Security tester and DevSecOps engineer with advanced skills in security assessment tool sets, networking exploitation, and Red & Blue Teaming, He has experience in website and mobile application security testing, DevSecOps setup, identifying and fixing security vulnerabilities, programming and content writing. He holds several badges in cybersecurity and Linux, and is ranked among the top 0.5% on TryHackme. Badges: Upwork, PentesterLab, Udemy, Parsehub, Hack The Box Academy (HTB-4B8852FF51).

Skills

Linux • Web Application Security • Python • PHP • DevOps • Troubleshooting • Technical writing • Cloud

Work Experience

Product Security Analyst

Oct 2022 - present

Studytonight Technologies Pvt. Ltd. • Full-time

Remote

Technologies: Linux • PHP • Security testing • NGINX • DevOps

I have reported and fixed 50+ critical vulnerabilities, done secure code review for website and APIs, and suggested several ideas for website improvement. set up Jenkins pipelines with code coverage and slack integration, optimized Docker images. published 150+ articles on various technical topics, such as Linux, DevOps, Apache, Nginx, Golang, StackOverflow and Security.

Technical Content Engineer

Jul 2022 – Sep 2022 • 2 mos

Studytonight Technologies Pvt. Ltd. • Internship

Remote

Technologies: Linux • Bash • Technical writing • UNIX • Gnu/linux

I joined Studytonight as a technical content engineer intern where I wrote Linux Server Administration articles. I provided helpful opinions to improve the website server and Security.

Freelance Technical Expert

Dec 2023 - present

Upwork & LinkedIn • Freelance

Remote

Technologies: UNIX • PHP • Bash • Python • PowerShell

- Application Security Testing & Consultation
- Troubleshooting, automating and fixing desktop, servers and Code related problems
- · Content writing Linux, Golang, Nginx, Apache, Bash, Cloud etc

Educations

Bachelor's degree: Science

Jul 2020 - May 2023 • 2 yrs 10 mos

Maharshi Dayanand Saraswati University, Ajmer

Ajmer, Rajasthan, India

Certifications & Awards

Cyber Security Professional - Google

Jun 2023

Advanced Python Programming - Mimo

Jul 2021

Network Security Expert - Fortinet

Apr 2022